[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the name of the neighborhood in which the 1980 movie The Changeling was set?", "correct_answer": "Chessman Park", "incorrect_answers": ["Grishom Park", "Marthas Vineyard", "Gorky Park"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The traditional Thai tea, called cha-yen in Thailand, is made from this type of tea.", "correct_answer": "Black tea", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "White tea", "Green tea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to urban legends, the Titantic sank because it was carrying which of the following?", "correct_answer": "A cursed mummy", "incorrect_answers": ["Jack the Ripper", "A man trying to outrun a gypsys curse", "The Book of the Dead"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Motown musical quartet, founded in Detroit, Michigan, scored their first #1 hit, I Cant Help Myself (Sugar Pie, Honey Bunch) in 1965.", "correct_answer": "The Four Tops", "incorrect_answers": ["The Temptetts", "The Temptations", "The Drifters"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which one of these statements about facial microexpressions is not true?", "correct_answer": "Microexpressions can be easily read by any person.", "incorrect_answers": ["Microexpressions are involuntary.", "Microexpressions can be controlled with certain types of chemicals.", "Microexpressions contain much more information than common expressions."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What sport are the Washington Generals associated with?", "correct_answer": "Basketball", "incorrect_answers": ["American Football", "Baseball", "Soccer"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Clara cells are found in this part of the human body.", "correct_answer": "Lungs", "incorrect_answers": ["Tongue", "Inner ear", "Eyes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these in not one of the traditional ingredients used for the preparation of the Greek salad?", "correct_answer": "Ham", "incorrect_answers": ["Cheese", "Onion", "Olives"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The actors playing Sally Hyde and Luke Martin in this drama film won the Best Actor and Best Actress Academy Awards.", "correct_answer": "Coming Home", "incorrect_answers": ["The English Patient", "Dances with Wolves", "Unforgiven"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If 2 people are eating the same number of calories per day, the one who eats frequent small meals will lose more weight than the one who eats one large meal per day.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is a vegetable with no homeland, dispersed all over the world.  In Egypt, it was worshipped for its spherical shape and concentric rings, believed to be symbols of eternity.", "correct_answer": "Onions", "incorrect_answers": ["Carrot", "Garlic", "Parsley"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the property used in this addition equation: 12 + 0 = 12?", "correct_answer": "Identity property", "incorrect_answers": ["Associative property", "Distributive property", "Commutative property"]}]